

phone: 206.618.6878

email: greenest@gmail.com

portfolio: www.rachelgreenedesign.com

linkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/greenerachel

about me

I am a UX designer building off my career in architecture – exploring good design principles, understanding user flows, and embracing negative space – shifting my focus on the digital world and how it impacts the user.

tools

Sketch3, Axure, Invision, POP, Omnigraffle, Balsamiq, Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Dreamweaver, CSS, HTML5, Revit, AutoCAD, SketchUp, Paper and Pen

skills

Information Architecture, Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristic Evaluations, Design Specs, Teamwork, Communication, Leadership

languages

English (native), Spanish

education

User Experience Immersive

General Assembly Seattle, Washington

UX Design

Career Foundry Online

Master of Architecture BS Architecture

Washington State University Pullman Washington

fun facts

- 1. I'm Architect 10779 in the State of Washington.
- 2. I spend my free time with my husband and daughter.
- 3. I've lived in 4 countries.

experience

UX Designer

Jan 2016 - present

Website for software security entrepreneur

skills: Prototyping, Research, Heuristic Evaluation, Wireframes, Information

Architecture, Design Specs

tools: Paper and Pen, Illustrator, Wordpress

Interaction Designer

Nov 2015 - Dec 2015

LoudBeacon

skills: Leadership, Prototyping, Research, Wireframes, Information Architecture,

Design Specs

tools: Sketch3, Illustrator, Marvel, Sketching, InDesign

UX Designer

Sept 2015- Dec 2015

General Assembly

FairWeather Camper | Web Application

skills: Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristics

tools: Sketch3, Invision, Sketching

Festival Application | Mobile Application

skills: Leadership, Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes,

Heuristics, Communication, Design Specs

tools: Axure, Sketching, InDesign

RGDesign | Portfolio Website

skills: Research, Prototyping, Usability Testing, Wireframes, Heuristics

tools: Sketching, sketch, HTML5, CSS

UX Designer Aug 2014 - Sept 2015

Epilog | Desktop Application

skills: Research, Wireframes, Heuristics, Communication

tools: Sketch3, Invision, Sketching

Architect Aug 2012- May 2014

Boxwood

Project Designer Aug 2010 - Aug 2012

Stock & Associates

Project Designer April 2008 - May 2009

Jones & Jones

Project Designer Nov 2007- April 2008

PB Architects

Municipal Development Volunteer June 2005 - July 2007

Peace Corps El Salvador